Hello friends, my name is Sachin
and today we are going to discuss about such people's
health booster China, so
friends, this is a super top-up health insurance
plan and today we will review its details, so
friends, first of all, let us know
why we need a topper brother, super top-up, so friends,
even today I have
seen such policies of many people in which the
cover of the entire family is only Rs. 3 or 4 lakh, Rs. 5 lakh,
but today it
is not sufficient for the entire family, so
you will not have to enhance your health insurance, you will have to
top it up, either
you can enhance it from your existing company
or you can take a new policy, so
increasing it is very important in today's date,
if you take a new policy, then
your premium is also very cheap in it and
nowadays some such new plans have come in which
you get a lot of benefits,
so friends, this is such people's
health booster, friends, this is such a plan in the market, there is a
feature in it which I will tell you later,
which till now I  According to the knowledge,
it is not available in any other plan of the market or in the topper plan,
so let us
start its review and
before moving ahead, let me tell you that if you are
new to my channel, then please
subscribe to it so that you will keep getting the latest
information related to insurance
and if you like this video, then do
not forget to share it
because knowledge increases by sharing, so
friends, if I talk about the benefit of this plan, then the
sum insured here is
Rs. 50 lakhs from five amounts and the
deductible option in this is deductible friends,
after which this plan will
work, that is, if you have chosen a
deductible of Rs. 3 here, then
this plan will be activated after Rs. 3 lakhs and
whatever amount you use from Rs. 5 lakhs to Rs. 50 lakhs,
it is fine, so we have three options in this.
You can buy this policy with its deductible of 45 lakhs and
can take an airplane fare of 5 lakhs to 50 lakhs.
If you have not understood the deductible,
then I will give you the link of the video here in the i button and
in the description, in
which I have explained it with complete examples,
you will understand it easily. So, if we
talk about Prevent Hospital, then
here CDS is free and you will get 90% post
hospitalization expenses, that is, the
expenses that you have paid
to the doctor before getting admitted in the hospital,
any lab test you have done, your
medicines and whatever expenses you have incurred after coming home from the same hospital, there will be
similar
dowry elements, friends, if we talk about room rent limit
here, then
you will get a single air conditioned private room here.
If we talk about treatment in this policy, then here there are 150 procedures for them,
so you go in the morning and come back in the evening, if these are
some such treatments, then those
dates for near idol surgery, all of them are
covered in it.  Talking about the no claim bonus,
friends, here
you will get a ten percent no claim bonus which will
go up to a maximum of 50%, that is, if suppose you have taken
an option of Rs 2000000 for
sum insured, then it will keep increasing by ten percent within it, that is,
your 50%, that is, up
to a maximum of 10 lakhs and which will keep increasing by
Rs 2 lakhs every year.
Reset benefit, friends,
these are the points which I was telling you
that till date, in all the super top up
lines that I have seen, there is no such feature anywhere that
your plan, suppose if you have taken a
plan of 40 lakhs or a plan of 25 lakhs
and if that ₹2500000 gets exhausted, then
here you will get the reset benefit, that is,
you will get ₹2500000 again,
which mostly happens in part base policies,
but it is also there in the super top up line,
but this will
not work in the same person or similar ones.  Okay, if
you have used it at home,
or if you have some other disease, or
if someone else in your family falls ill
in that year, then you
can avail the benefit. So friends, many people get
confused here as to what is Topper and what is
Super Top, so
I have made a complete video on that too, the
link of which I will give in the description in the i button,
so you will understand very well what is the
difference between the topic on Super Top. As of
today, 90% of the companies
launch Super Topper plan, I will
tell you the basic features, what is the difference between
these two topics, in which
every bill should be above your diploma, that
is, if you have given a three lakh dutiable award, then the
value of every moment
should be above Rs 3 lakh there, but
what happens in Super Top Up,
if it is collected and sold in three ways in the whole year, suppose
even by doing one like, the bill comes to Rs 3 lakh,
whatever bill is above that, this
Super Topper will pay you, so
friends, let's talk about the
treatment here today.  Come, this treatment
is available here, if you are given
Ayurvedic medicines, Siddha medicines,
Unani medicines in the hospital, then that will also be
covered here. If we talk about the ambulance cover,
friends, then here one percent sum
insured means, suppose you have
taken a plan of Rs. 1000000 here, then
you should get Rs. 10,000 here, but the maximum
limit of the company is Rs. 5000, that is,
you will not get entries for ambulance more than Rs. 5000. If we
talk like this,
friends, the most unique
thing here is that if there is a child above six years of age,
he can also take this point
individually and there is
no limit on the maximum, any
healthy person, even if he is 70 years or 75 years old, can
also take this line. If we talk about
new born baby care different child,
then here the new born baby whose
parents are already above age can take
their children for treatment under the Astro Turf line.  You can add it after the age of 90, the
question arises only at the time of renewal
and along with this, the age limit for dependent children is
21 years, that is, you
can cover a maximum of children up to the age of 10 years in a family,
friends, here there is a claim service guarantee
that you will get a cashless claim within four hours
and you will get reimbursement within 14 days,
if both these deadlines are exceeded
then the company will charge you a penalty here, till now
you will hardly get an option of 10% service guarantee in any other policy
which is written in the brochure,
I will give you the link in its description, from
here you can download its Splendor Pro,
if we talk about policy depression, friends, if you
take a 2 year policy here then you will get a
discount of 10% and if you take a 3 year
policy then
you will get a discount of up to 12 and a half percent on all the premiums,
health checkup is available
every year in this, friends, if you have a floater
policy in which there are 2802 kids or two digits
or one kid  So here you will get two
health checkups every year.
Talking about the luxury program,
friends, it is available here, like if you
participate in a marathon or you have
joined a gym or you have done
any such fitness activity and
you will share its information with the company, then
you will get some points
and you can use these points as OPD benefit, by
catching those points
you can get the OPD removed from there, so
friends, there is an optional news inside this plan,
this is your base plan,
if you do not want to
add something else in my friend, then
here we have option one, option two,
you can take it,
our first option is Hospital Delhi,
this is ₹1000 which
you will get in silver as per this rate and you will get folds at the rate of ₹3000 per day,
friends, the hospitalization here should be for three days
and the maximum rate  Okay, there is
a convenience benefit in this, friends,
that is, if wherever
your hospitalization is for more than 10 or 12 months, then
this hospital will be given
to the staff of Delhi, along with that
you will also get condensed benefits, in that you will get a
lump sum of Rs. 10,000 in Silver and
Rs. 20,000 in Gold will be
deposited in your account, this is Option One, if
you use both the options then
you will get this benefit, if
we talk about the options here, then there are two
things that you will get in this channel,
first is personal accident, if
you use Silver then you will get a cover of Rs. 10, if you use Gold then
you will get a cover of Rs. 20 lakh,
if your president here is this,
you get it in case of your death due to an accident,
but if you do not die
and you become temporarily disabled, then
what will the company do here, they will provide you Rs. 5000
weekly in Silver for the next 10 weeks
and you will get Rs. 10,000 in Gold,
that too for the next 10 weeks.  For weeks,
you will get this additional benefit under this.
Secondly, if you
die in an accident under this, then here
you will get the money for bringing the body.
Return of Romance is
50,000 for you in Silver and 1 lakh for Gold.
Meaning, suppose you were in some such place outside
or you are out of the country where you
die and whatever expenses are incurred in bringing your body back to
India to your home,
you can take it here in Maximum Nimbus.
Friends, here is the critical illness
cover, so the critical illness cover is of
Rs 5 lakh, you will get it under Silver
and Rs 10 lakh in Gold. This is also
searched. Friends, there are some specific
diseases, there are 18 to 20 diseases.
If you have any doubt about any disease,
then the money is immediately deposited in your account.
So friends, these are some of the benefits of the bank.
Let us talk about what are the
negatives in it and the exclusions of this bank.
What is it, friends, first of all
we talk about 2 years
waiting period here,
you should declare any of your pre-existing diseases
like suppose you had thyroid or you had
any heart problem, Meena, have you ever
undergone any surgery or suppose you
are diabetic, similarly if you have had any
such diseases and you delete them then you will
not get cover for those diseases for 2 years,
along with this the waiting period of 2 years is for
some such disease like you have had
thyroid, you have had joint
replacement, you have stone, you have had sinus
surgery, you have had surgery for equal battery stone, then
you will
not get cover for all these things for 2 years,
friends there is a waiting period of 30 days
in every plate, here also
you will not get any cover for 30 days, you will get it
only in case of accidental injury,
friends let me repeat it to you once again
that
whatever your dutiable amount has been used for this policy,
it will be only after its completion.  It
will be activated friends, there is also a co-payment of 20% here,
that is, if you have to buy this policy
after the age of 45, if you have
bought the policy before the age of 45, then you will
not have to make any payment of any kind.
If you have to buy this policy after the age of 45
and after that your age has reached sixty years,
okay, then after the age of 60,
you will have to pay 20% on any claim that comes,
friends, if you
called home 1 lakh rupees, then the company will give 80 thousand rupees,
you will give 20,000 rupees. If you have
bought this policy at the age of 45
and suppose in childhood, a claim comes in a year for 50,000, then
you will get the full amount, but as soon as your
age is above sixty years, then a co-
payment of 40% will be applied here, so
friends, I hope you have understood this plan
and thank you very much
for watching this video, see you
in the next video. If you have any questions
related to this line, then you can WhatsApp me.  You
can do it, you can message, you
can comment, you can email,
you will get all the details in the description box.